Episode 2           Confession?
This is your little sister, Nanakura?
She seems a lot younger than you!
She's in her first year
of elementary school.
What a cutie.
I always end up spoiling her.
Man, must be nice having
a little sister... wish I had one.
Can I have another piece
of candy? Onii-chan.
And now I have one?!
Hang on, there's no reason she needs
to be in elementary school.
I guess I ended up basing
her on my own sister...
Kind of an airhead call, huh?
I mean, that was...!
That said, you being an airheaded big
sister is a major plus, Nanakura!
A plus?
What kind of sister
stuff do you normally do?
I kind of treat her like a kitten.
I pat her head and squish her cheeks...
That sounds great. I wouldn't mind
a nice big sister, either.
Were you about to squish my cheeks?!
That'd be going too far, even for me!
For a long time
What's that there?
A line I wanted to learn today.
"I'm so scared. Is it okay if I sleep
with you tonight, Onii-chan?"
That is not what it says!
You sure?
You really oughta learn that one too!
Better write it down!
I'm not going to bother...
For a long time
this place has been          I'm so scared
No!
I messed up!
Ha, I got you to do it.
There are a lot of lines I actually
need to memorize!
Here, you can use my blank slate hands, too.
I hate you, big brother!
She's in her rebellious phase?!
But I guess there are some lines you can
memorize without writing them down, huh?
It's not like that!
N... Nanakura?
Oh, I'm practicing.
I need to rehearse crying.
Oh, you were acting! That's a relief!
I almost gave you a big hug.
I can't stop crying because of you.
W-W-Wait—
Please, stop being so kind to me.
I'm so sorry! I honestly can't deal
with this sort of thing!
I didn't really expect you to be able to
handle someone who's crying,
but that was just sad.
What if I was crying for real?
Why are you making that face?!
I figured the best way to cheer
you up would be with a funny face.
I'm not that immature—
Cut it out!
To credit his own lie,
he did believe he was indeed
the Duke of Milan, out of the substitution.
Hence, his ambition growing—
Dost thou hear?
Your tale, sir, would cure deafness.
To have no screen between
this part he played
and him he played it for,
he needs will be Absolute Milan.
Here cease more questions.
Thou art inclined to sleep, Miranda.
Come away, servant, come. I am ready now.
Approach, my Ariel.
All hail, great master Prospero!
I come to answer thy best pleasure.
63rd
Kouban
Fes
Be it to fly, to swim...
Sixty-Third Kouban High School Culture Festival
Yakisoba
Sixty-Third Kouban High
School Culture Festival
Custard
Chocolate
Mini-Cream Puffs
These are adorable!
I'll get you one. Which do you want?
I can't decide!
You pick, Senpai.
Chocolate!
Spoiled-chan would
definitely pick chocolate!
And I bet Imp-chan would go for strawberry.
You wanna do something
bittersweet with me, huh?
No! That's not it at all!
Isn't it, though?
And Tsundere-chan likes lemon, right?
Are you buying snacks for every character?!
I want to get some for everybody!
I take it Cool-chan wants mint?
J-Just one is fine, really!
You sure that's enough?
The others won't get discouraged?
You're not gonna turn into DiscouRin-chan?
Don't make my name into a pun, please.
Which do you want then, Rin-chan?
C-Custard is fine...
Y'know, I like plain best too, actually.
Senpai, are you sick?!
Yeah. It's not too bad—
You poor thing. I wish
I could take your place...
Say what, now?
Uh, just...
If it came from you, I wouldn't
mind getting sick, maybe.
Nanakura, you're such an angel.
I'm feeling a little better now.
Th-That was Spoiled-chan just now, though!
Okay?
Oh, it was? I must be out of it...
Are you sure you're gonna be okay?
Y-Yeah. I think I'm gonna go home
after resting up a bit.
I-I guess I could walk
you home, if you want!
To be honest, I was kinda anxious
about going back alone.
Having you along would be a real relief.
Th-That was Tsundere-chan
who offered, though...
Put this on, Nanakura.
Higher-Dimension Mask
Can't risk you actually getting sick.
He's acting different
because of how sick he is...
And he said it'd be a relief
to have me with him...
Oh, no, I can't stop grinning!
But he won't notice as long as
I'm wearing my mask, right?
I think my fever's died down...
Senpai, how are you feeling?
Nanakura? Don't you need
to head home by now?
I'm fine. And... I made dinner.
This is great! Who made it? Cool-chan?
Oh, come on.
You're right back at it
the second you feel better.
To be honest, I don't remember much
about what happened...
How'd I get changed and whatnot?
I... helped.
Nanakura...
I-It was Imp-chan!
More like Naughty-chan.
I am not Naughty-chan!
If you're going to be like that,
I won't look after you next time!
Does that mean no more udon?!
I guess I can make it for you again,
when you're feeling better...
Awesome!
Y'know,
I think guys who can tell girls how they
feel are cool and probably popular, too.
Senpai... do you have a crush on someone?
W-What is it?
From the first time we met, I...
I've thought...
That I liked you, Tsundere-chan!
What do you think of the confession?
Would it work?
Where did that even come from?!
You need to think more about the atmosphere!
It's going to be a moment to remember, okay?
The atmosphere, huh? Okay...
How's this?
Manufactured city lights?!
I just...
keep finding myself looking at you
instead of the starry sky.
And that makes sense,
because you're the most beautiful.
I want to remember this moment,
when I was able
to reach out and touch
a star like you, Cool-chan!
Are you saying you like me?
Uh, well... yes... that's it.
I see.
Hngh!
I want to be the one making
hearts throb... It's not fair!
So, did that star stuff
sound too stupid, or...?
I thought it was nice.
For real?
I kinda assumed that you preferred
a more casual approach, Nanakura.
That is also nice.
So you're not particular?
I'm embarrassed to admit it, but no...
But that's awesome.
My friends have laughed at me
for not having a type, though.
BLUNT!
For guys like me,
that's a huge relief, though.
It's hard to guess what girls like.
Well, I better take this down...
I was going to ask
if he likes someone, but...
I guess it's fine.
I guess it's snowing.
Say, are you sure you wanna stick with me?
They're probably partying
in the club room right now.
Didn't you have a lot
of stuff you needed to carry?
I'm a real macho man!
A few bags isn't gonna...
Then how are you gonna hold an umbrella?
I guess you could take one and—
It's Christmas, so...
Cool-chan is in a romantic mood?!
Is this a Christmas miracle?!
What is it?
I was just imagining you, me,
Squeeze
and Cool-chan all under
the umbrella together.
I wanna join in, too.
Great, another one!
I forgot my umbrella too, actually.
They just keep coming!
I guess if you want me under there
that badly, I don't mind!
I'll just buy umbrellas for the rest of you!
That's a lot of people
under this umbrella, huh?
Sounds like a recipe for a fight.
Guess I'm glad it's just
you and me, Nanakura.
I-I guess so...
Pseudo
Harem
Why's winter break so long?! I miss Senpai!
Kitahama-senpai
Hello?
Hello...
Hey, Nanakura. What's up?
Why aren't you talking?
I called without thinking
of anything to talk about!
Wait, is that you, Cool-chan?!
Yes. I wanted to hear your voice.
C-Could I get some more
whisper voice over the phone,
please, please, please, please?
But I'm the one who wanted to hear you.
So, did you need something?
Um...
I miss you.
Nanakura, you called
because you're bored, didn't you?
He thought I was Cool-chan just now...
Well, if you're that bored,
we could go to a shrine for New Years.
I'll go!
Whoa, don't scare me like that!
A little quieter, please.
What do you think, Senpai?
Awesome...
You cold?
Just my hands.
Here you go. A hand warmer.
Thank you.
It's not warm at all, though...
Yeah, I actually used it yesterday.
Please don't go into
actual Cool-chan!
You are acting right now, aren't you?!
I mean, my hands are really warm!
Your hands!
Check it out!
Wow, that is cold.
I guess you're physically
embodying Cool-chan now.
Could I use... this instead
of the hand-warmer?
Well... if you don't mind me
napping until you're good.
Your hands are warm because
you're feeling sleepy, aren't you?
Fortunes!
Fortunes
Well, we need one for everybody, so that's...
One, two, three, four, five...
Six fortunes?
No, just two is fine!
Are you sure you don't mind, Spoiled-sensei?!
I wanna keep drawing
until we both have "Best Fortune!"
I think we'll start with twenty, then.
I'm afraid you can't...
Please, don't!
You okay?
I... might not be... I think.
Are you hurting anywhere?
I think I'm having a heart attack...
It's that bad?!
Fortune
Future Good Luck
Nanakura, how'd your fortune go?
I got Best Fortune!
Wow, awesome!
Bad Luck
Wait, that says Bad!
Is that why you tripped before?
Best Fortune!
Huh? Nanakura?
Snap out of it! You wanna draw another one?
Best Fortune!
Library
Whatcha studying for, Nanakura?
I'm trying to study a bit at a time
so I'll be ready when exams roll around.
I wouldn't bother. We're never
gonna be one of the smart ones.
The... The law of sines!
What... What even is that?!
You think you can just whip
out some complicated words?!
I was hoping I could share
more secrets with Cool-chan.
I'd rather share memories than secrets.
Do you want to study with me?
Dammit! I haven't forgotten that 29 you got!
Shhh about that!
Come to think of it,
why are you here, Senpai?
I wanted a big book that we could
use as a prop, but they said no,
so I'm headed to the clubroom
to make one instead.
But there's no club today...
That's right.
Guess I'm the only one coming
into the office today.
Just the two of us...!
We can be
alone together!
Um...
I-I could help you out, if you want.
Nanakura-san?
I thought you were gonna study diligently.
I can start tomorrow. Yeah.
Let's both get awful test
scores again then, Nanakura!
Quiet in the library
Sun's already down.
Come take a look, Nanakura.
See? Nice view, right?
I don't even care right now!
Whatcha think?
U-Um...
Yes! It is very cute!
Yes, but you're cuter still.
W-What are you saying?!
I'm not cute for your sake!
I gotta ask, calling a night
view cute? What's up with that?
W-What are you talking about?
I mean, you were talking about the view...
Actually, that place over there looks
like a face, and that's pretty cute.
Wh-Where are you talking about?
Look! Over there, see?
Where?
But you're cuter still, Nanakura.
You just wanted to say
that again, didn't you?!
I wish I knew how Senpai felt about me...
Even though it's scary.
I'm having a hard time
holding back lately...
I want you to like me too, Senpai!
That's what Spoiled-chan would say.
I like you.
Cool-chan would come right out and say it...
Senpai... How does...
How does he really feel?
I don't think I'm gonna get any sleep.
I hope I can tell him someday.
But when's someday?
Three days from now? Next month? Next year?
Maybe he'll randomly confess
to me tomorrow...
The truth is... I...
The Amnesiacs
I can't remembler...
Remambler? Remeblor?
Senpai, that's a little too much stumbling!
I don't think I'm gonna be a proper actor.
I can't see how this helps
you rehearse, Nanakura...
Maybe I should give you private lessons?
I'll get a job so I can pay you!
Maybe, if you get better,
I wouldn't mind co-starring with you!
Your acting is just fantastic, Nanakura.
Me too!
Um, well... Acting around you, it's...
I really like it.
W-What do you think? Of that performance?
Come on, that was all you.
I can tell the difference by now, y'know?
It was acting! Acting acting acting acting!
Yeah?
Well, I like... your acting too, Nanakura!
Come on!
Much Ado About Nothing
Much Ado About Nothing!
Since we have the day off,
let's go somewhere, Senpai.
Come on now, I'm not your senpai anymore.
I'm a Nanakura too, now.
Oh, the premise is he married
into the family, huh?